Tooltip_EN = {
    Tooltip_MoreMedicalWarning86 = "Placeholder. If you find this text, please contact the staff with a screenshot.",
    Tooltip_MoreMedicalWarning87 = "Placeholder. If you find this text, please contact the staff with a screenshot.",
    Tooltip_MoreMedicalWarning88 = "Placeholder. If you find this text, please contact the staff with a screenshot.",

    Tooltip_BurnTreatment = "A cream with a similar texture to tiger balm.<br>Helps heal burns.<br>If a patient with blood phobia uses it, the panic level increases.",
    Tooltip_SealedBandage = "A sterile bandage wrapped in plastic.<br>If the plastic is removed, a sterile bandage is inside.",
    
    Tooltip_PillsCommercialPainkillers = "It's longer lasting than ordinary painkillers.<br>Of course, it's not real Tylenol.",
    Tooltip_PillsPrescriptionPainkillers = "It's longer lasting and stronger than homemade Tylenol.<br>But do you know what ER means?",
    Tooltip_PillsCaffeine = "Coffee powder frozen and dried, mixed with flour, and compressed.",
    Tooltip_PillsCommercialAntibiotic = "Antibiotics from the pharmacy, mixed with various herbs to make the
    Tooltip_PillsCommercialSedative = "It's stronger than the usual sedative.<br>It calms the mind and makes you sleepy.",
    Tooltip_PillsPharmacyPrescription = "Various unknown drugs are mixed together.<br>It can be used as a material to enhance the effect of homemade drugs.<br>It may be dangerous if taken without proper processing.",
    
    Tooltip_SyretteHighGradePainkillers = "It's not real morphine, but it's made into a syringe to make it stronger.<br>If you get multiple shots at once, there may be a serious side effect.",
    Tooltip_SyretteAdrenalin = "It's made into a syringe so it can be injected directly into the bloodstream.<br>If you get multiple shots at once, there may be a serious side effect.",
    Tooltip_SyrettePrescriptionAntibiotic = "A syringe made by mixing homemade antibiotics with recyclable antibiotics.<br>If you get multiple shots at once, there may be a serious side effect.",
    Tooltip_SyrettePrescriptionSedatives = "A strong sedative that contains psychoactive ingredients.<br>If you get multiple shots at once, there may be a serious side effect.",
    Tooltip_BottleFluMedication = "A homemade flu medication made from natural ingredients.<br>It feels like a relief when you drink it all at once.",
    Tooltip_PowderPackFluMedication = "A flu medication made by mixing various herbs.<br>It's easy to carry and has a better effect than ordinary homemade flu medication.",
    Tooltip_PowderPackHemostatic = "A hemostatic that is applied to the wound.<br>It can be used to stop bleeding.",
    
    Tooltip_Tourniquet = "A homemade tourniquet made by tying a rubber band.<br>If you tie it around your neck, the carotid artery can be blocked and an emergency situation can occur.",
    
    Tooltip_BottleCoughSyrup = "A homemade cough syrup made by folk remedies.<br>It can reduce coughing and sneezing for about 1~2 hours.",
    Tooltip_NasalSpray = "A medicine that suppresses coughing and sneezing.<br>It can reduce coughing and sneezing for about 4~5 hours.",

    Tooltip_EmergencySurgeryKit = "A surgery kit for treating critical injuries.<br>It is used when treating a fallen person.",
    Tooltip_LightWeightEmergencySurgeryKit = "A surgery kit for treating critical injuries.<br>It is used when treating a fallen person.<br>It is specially processed to be very light.",

    Tooltip_BagRunnerSatchel = "A simple bag that runners often use.<br>It can be worn at the same time as a backpack.",
    Tooltip_BardGuitarAcoustic = "A guitar that can be used as both a weapon and an instrument.<br>It can be used as a weapon when you swing it, or you can play some nice songs with it.<br>When the song ends, the guitar is destroyed.",
    Tooltip_DeathFlag = "Is it over? Is this the end? When I return to my hometown, I will confess my feelings to her! And so on... There are many ominous words written there.<br>For about 40 seconds, the zombies ignore the survivors around them and rush towards me.",
}
